pcrichard.com 2012-12-25

# HDTVs, Appliances, Cameras, Computers & More On Sale at P. C. Richard & Son

Privacy Policy

P.C. Richard & Son (hereafter referred to as "we' , 'us' or "our") understands that you care about how your personal information is used and, as a result, we take your privacy seriously. This policy will explain, among other things, what information we collect and how we use the information we collect online.

By accessing and using our web-site you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Information we collect:**

We collect personally identifiable information such as your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number(s) (including mobile/cell phones), credit card(s) number, and birth date ("Personal Information") when you make a purchase from us or when you register on our site.

We may also collect non-personal information, such as your interests, gender, zip or area codes, when you visit our web-site. This information does not allow a third party to identify you individually. We may also collect non-personal information by the use of cookies. The use of cookies is common on the internet and most websites use them to collect information such as your IP address, your hardware model, operating system, the type of browser you use, the sites you have visited as well as items you have viewed on our web site and other sites.

**What are cookies?**  
A cookie is a small data file that is sent by web sites to your hard drive by your computer's browser. Cookies and other technologies such as web beacons or tags are used to measure the effectiveness of our ads and to determine the display of content and advertising to you based on your interests both on our site and other web sites you may visit. We may use one or more companies to place advertisements for our products and services and those of third parties on our web site and third party sites. We and companies whom we have contracted with, may use anonymous information about your visits to our site and other sites. The information collected and used by this process is always anonymous, and does not enable any third-party to identify you personally.

Most web browsers will have information explaining how to prevent your web browser from accepting a new cookie, notifying you when one is stored, and how to disable or erase cookies. Take a look at your web browser for instructions on how this is done. This information can usually be found in the "Help" section.

**Use of Mobile Devices:**  
If you visit our web site from your mobile device, you may know that certain mobile service providers uniquely identify mobile devices. We or our third-party service providers may receive such information if you visit our web site through your mobile device. Some mobile service providers operate systems that identify the physical location of a device that uses that service. We or our third-party providers may receive such information. The physical location services on most mobile devices can be disabled. Contact your mobile service provider if you have any questions on how to do this.

**Children's Privacy:**  
The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") regulates how and what personal information websites may collect from children under 13. This site is for use by a general audience and is not directed at or intended to be used by children. In our attempts to protect the privacy of children, P.C. Richard & Son does not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

**How we use this information:**  
We may use the information we collect from you for a variety of purposes. These include, but are not limited to; processing your order for the purchase of products or services from us; delivering, installing or servicing products you purchased from us; to communicate with you marketing and advertising; and other promotions and surveys. 

**Information Sharing:**  
We do not sell or rent your Personal Information to any third parties. We may share your Personal Information with our affiliate or subsidiary companies and with service providers who need to know this to provide support services for us such as delivery, servicing of products, shipping, credit card processing or issuance of our private label credit card.

There may be times when we are required to share Personal Information with law enforcement or regulatory agencies in accordance with a court order, subpoena or a regulation or where we believe in good faith that it is required by law.

To help us improve your shopping experience and to better serve you, we may also share non-personal information about visitors to our web-site with third party companies who analyze information such as what web-sites you have visited or we may allow these third party companies to collect information on our website by using cookies.

**Security:**  
We use reasonable security measures to protect your Personal Information. When you enter Personal Information during an online transaction/order on our web site it is encrypted using secure socket layering technology. While we take reasonable security measures to protect your Personal Information, due to the open nature of the Internet, no security measure is 100% effective against the actions of those who may gain unauthorized access, such as hackers. Therefore, we cannot guarantee the effectiveness of these security measures.

**Information you may access and "Opt-Out" choices:**  
If you open an online account with us, you can review your Personal Information, add to it or update it by clicking on the "Your Account" section of the site.

We may occasionally send you emails with advertisements for sales or information about other promotional events. If you want to "opt out" of receiving these emails you can do so by clicking the "Unsubscribe link" located at the bottom of our promotional emails which will remove you from our email list.

**Links to other web sites:**  
This site may contain links to other web sites which are independent of us and over whom we have no control. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such non-affiliated sites and disclaim any liability for those sites or their content. You should read the privacy policies of these other sites before disclosing any Personal Information to them.

**Updates:**  
We may occasionally update this policy. If we make any material changes to this policy, we will post a notice of such changes here. We reserve the right, in our discretion, to make changes at any time. Please check this policy occasionally for any updates. The last update was October 2012.
